Step into the zone, heart's a drum, feel the beat
Every breath a testament, blastin' from the streets
Sweat drips, clock ticks, I'm in the rhythm's embrace
Mindset of a warrior, doubts erased, no trace
Swishin' past the limits, let the fire ignite
Every rep, every set, soarin' high in the night
Chevy in the heart with the lion's roar
Breakin' through the barriers, always cravin' more
Explode, you got this, boom boom, let's go
Feel the power rise and let your spirit glow
Explode, you got this, boom boom, ignite
With every step forward, you're takin' flight
In the gym, in the zone, where legends are born
Every drop of sweat, a crown that's worn
Feel the burn, let it churn, unleash the beast
On this path to greatness, never retreat, feast
Eyes on the prize with a laser focus
Every challenge faced, just hocus pocus
Fear's just a shadow in the light of my will
Climbin' every mountain with an iron skill
Explode, you got this, boom boom, let's go
Feel the power rise and let your spirit glow
Explode, you got this, boom boom, ignite
With every step forward, you're takin' flight
Feel the rhythm flow like rivers in your veins
Every step, every move, breakin' all the chains
Rise up, stand tall, let the world hear your call
With a heart full of fire, you'll never fall
Explode, you got this, boom boom, let's go
Feel the power rise and let your spirit glow
Explode, you got this, boom boom, ignite
With every step forward, you're taking flight
Feel the rhythm flow like rivers in your veins
Every step, every move, breaking all the chains
Rise up, stand tall, let the world hear your call
With a heart full of fire, you'll never fall
Push the limits, break the mold
With every beat, let your story unfold
Champion at heart, with a fire that won't quit
In this game of life, you're the ultimate hit
Explode, you got this, boom boom, let's go
Feel the power rise and let your spirit glow