by RentAnAdviser.com
Gassed up, yeah, yeah
Why would you wanna bring
somethin' between us?
There's nothin' between
us, oh, ayy, ayy
Why would you wanna use
a life to keep us?
To keep us together, oh woah, oh
Better when we're both apart (Oh)
Better when we're both apart
We're no good for each other
No good for each other
Better when we're both apart (My baby)
Better when we're both apart
We're no good for each other
A lonely night
Baby girl, I loved you
on a lonely night, oh
It was the only time
And if I led you on, then I apologize
How can I make you rethink
your decision?
Unruly decision, oh woah, hey (Oh)
What's gonna make you rethink
your position?
I know your intentions (I know your
intentions), oh woah, oh, hey
Better when we're both apart (Oh)
Better when we're both apart
We're no good for each other
No good for each other (No
good for each other)
Better when we're both apart (My baby)
Better when we're both apart
We're no good for each other
A lonely night
Baby girl, I loved you on a lonely
night, oh (Ooh woah)
It was the only time
And if I led you on, then I apologize,
oh (I apologize)
Better when we're both apart (I'll be)
Better when we're both apart (Oh)
We're no good for each other
No good for each other
Better when we're both
apart (Oh, baby)
Better when we're both apart
We're no good for each other, hey
A lonely night
Baby girl, I loved you on
a lonely night, oh (Hey)
It was the only time (It
was the only time)
And if I led you on, then I apologize,
oh (Apologize, woah)
A lonely night
Baby girl, I loved you on a lonely
night, oh (Ooh woah)
It was the only time
And if I led you on, then
I apologize, oh (Oh)
Baby girl, I loved you
You know I loved you
Know I loved you
Hey, no-no-no-no-no
No-no-no-no-no, ayy
by RentAnAdviser.com